const questions = [
  {
    question: 'Javascript is an _______ language?',
    answers: ['object-oriented', 'object-based', 'procedural', 'none of the above'],
    correctAnswer: 'object-oriented' 
  },
  {
    question: 'Commonly used data types do not include:',
    answers: ['strings', 'booleans', 'alerts', 'numbers'],
    correctAnswer: 'alerts' 
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following keywords is used to define a variable in Javascript?',
    answers: ['var', 'let', 'both a and b', 'none of the above'],
    correctAnswer: 'both a and b' 
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following methods is used to access HTML elements using Javascript?',
    answers: ['getElementByID()', 'getElementsByClassName()', 'both a and b', 'none of the above'],
    correctAnswer: 'both a and b'
  },
  {
    question: 'You can use a text string as a literal value or assign it to a variable.',
    answers: ['true', 'false'],
    correctAnswer: 'true'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following methods can be used to display data in some form using Javascript?',
    answers: ['document.Write()', 'console.log()', 'window.alert()', 'all the above'],
    correctAnswer: 'all the above' 
  },
  {
    question: 'JavaScript is a programming language used for creating dynamic and interactive web pages.',
    answers: ['true', 'false',],
    correctAnswer: 'true' 
  },
  {
    question: 'In JavaScript, the typeof operator is used to determine the data type of a variable.',
    answers: ['true', 'false',],
    correctAnswer: 'true' 
  },
  {
    question: 'JavaScript is a not case-sensitive language, meaning that variable and Variable are considered different variables.',
    answers: ['true', 'false',],
    correctAnswer: 'false' 
  },
  {
    question: 'JavaScript supports both synchronous and asynchronous programming.',
    answers: ['true', 'false',],
    correctAnswer: 'true' 
  }
];